Hello...
motor insurance department...
Oh hello...
I'd like to ask about insurance for my car.
Yes, of course.
I'll just take a few details.
What's your name?
Patrick Jones.
And your address?
It's 27 Bank Road.
27 Bank Road.
Is that in Greendale?
Yes.
And what's your daytime phone number?
My work number is 730453.
And could I ask what your occupation is?
Dentist.
OK...
now a few details about your car...
What size is the engine?
It's 1200 CCS.
Thank you...
and the make and model?
It's a Hewton Sable.
Could you spell the model name please?
Yes...
S-A-B-L-E.
Ah yes.., thanks.
And when was it made?
1997.
Lovely...
right...
I presume you've had a previous insurer?
Yes.
Right...
we need to know the name of the company.
Yes...
it was Northern Star.
Thank you,
and have you made any insurance claims in the last five years?
Yes...
one in 1999.
And what was the problem?
It was stolen...
but...
That's fine, Mr Jones...
that's all we need to know at the moment...
And will there be any other named drivers?
Just the one...
And his name?
Simon Paynter.
Could you spell the surname please?
P-A-Y-N-T-E-R.
OK thank you...
And what relationship is he to you?
He's my brother-in-law.
And what will you or Mr Paynter be using the car for?
Well...
mainly for social use...
Social use (murmuring).
Will you be using it to travel to work?
Yes...
sometimes.
...Anything else?
No.
That's it...
And finally...
when would you like to start the insurance?
I'll need it from the 31st of January.
Right...
Mr Jones...
I'm getting a couple of quotes coming up on the computer now...
and the best bet looks like being with a company called Red Flag.
Yeah.
And that comes out at $450 per year...
Well...
that seems OK...
it's quite a bit lower than I've been paying up to now...
Great...
so would you like me to go ahead with that?
Sure...
why not?
How would you like to pay?